(Howard:)Yeah, well, Bernadette's a little
under the weather and my mom's...
(Howard:)...kind of under my dentist.
(Raj:)Wait, your...
Your mother's sleeping with your dentist?
(Howard:)Former dentist. I need a new one
now that I know where his hands have been.
(Raj:)So you're wandering
all around by yourself?
That's not the hero's welcome
an astronaut should come home to.
(Howard:)It's okay. You know, we space cowboys
don't do what we do for glory and fame.
(Howard:)We leave that to your rock stars,
and your athletes...
(Howard:)...and your Howie Mandels.
(Stuart:)Oh, hey, man, welcome back.
(Howard:)Oh, Stuart, thanks.
What are you doing here?
(Stuart:)- I kind of live here now.
- Just until he gets back on his feet.
(Raj:)Which are looking pretty good
in the boots I bought him for his birthday.
(Stuart:)Ah, he's spoiling me and I love it.